{
  "2": [
    { "prompt": "io", "answer": "sono" },
    { "prompt": "tu", "answer": "sei" },
    { "prompt": "lui", "answer": "è" },
    { "prompt": "lei", "answer": "è" },
    { "prompt": "sono", "answer": "io/loro" },
    { "prompt": "sei", "answer": "tu" },
    { "prompt": "è", "answer": "lui/lei" }
  ],
  "3": [
    { "prompt": "io", "answer": "ho" },
    { "prompt": "tu", "answer": "hai" },
    { "prompt": "lui", "answer": "ha" },
    { "prompt": "lei", "answer": "ha" },
    { "prompt": "ho", "answer": "io" },
    { "prompt": "hai", "answer": "tu" },
    { "prompt": "ha", "answer": "lui/lei" }
  ]
}
